<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>If Only You Set Me Free on</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in If Only You Set Me Free on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://book.pyxelm.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/the-sharadith/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/the-sharadith/</guid><description>Chapter One (In the 33rd year of the reign of High Matriarch Ramsen of the Empire of the Petrified Child)</description></item><item><title>Alucinara Energy</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/alucinara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/alucinara/</guid><description>Overview Alucinara, also known as magic, is a form of energy that alters the ways in which the natural world can operate.</description></item><item><title>Bushdeer</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/bushdeer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/bushdeer/</guid><description>Overview Bushdeer (Type Species spp. Floricervus Floricervus), native to the steppes of the 2nd and -1st realms, are a type of deer related to the Sika deer of Earth.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Gnats</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/cloud-gnats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/cloud-gnats/</guid><description>Overview Cloud Gnats are animal-like apparitions made of aluciferous dust. They commonly appear as small animals, standing upright with their abdomen tapering off into a wispy tail.</description></item><item><title>Coroth</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/coroth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/coroth/</guid><description>Overview Coroth was a Morellic city state founded in the Minikin Neolithic Era. It preceeded the Corothic Republic, a nation that would greatly influence the surrounding regions including the Empire of the Petrified Child, which succeeded Sarvara.</description></item><item><title>Demi-Slugs</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/demi-slugs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/demi-slugs/</guid><description>%% What are the significant features which make this relevant to the plot? What patterns are there when it comes to description and properties?</description></item><item><title>Dragons</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/dragons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/dragons/</guid><description>Overview Dragons are a diminutive amphibian species native to the wetlands of the 2nd, 3rd, and -2nd realms. They are capable of flight through the use of alucinara and mainly feed upon small berries, bark, and insects.</description></item><item><title>Early History of the Minikin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/history/early-minikin-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/history/early-minikin-history/</guid><description>Timeline 5 MYA Minikin begin to diverge from the lineage that would become red squirrels Minikin ancestors are shifted from the 0th realm to the 2nd due to supernova 3 MYA The genus Anthrosciurus diverges from Sciurus Anthrosciurids begin to use tools 1 MYA Anthrosciurids begin to use fire and magic Language is developed in Anthrosciurids 300,000 YA Early Minikin evolve into Modern Minikin (Anthrosciurus arborensis) in northern Tséireph 200,00 YA First wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Eastern Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis occidentalis) migrate to the eastern continent and eastern islands Modern Minikin spread across whole of Tséireph 175,000 YA Second wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Southern Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis australis) migrate to southwestern continent 50,000 YA Third and final wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Insular Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis insulensis) diverge from Southern Minikin and continue to migrate south to the southwestern archipelago The various Minikin subspecies begin to spread and cohabitate with other races 10,000 YA Agriculture begins to be practised by Minikin, originating in fluvial areas with seasonal floods, especially the mediterranean-climate Sarvaran river basin.</description></item><item><title>Every Force of Nature</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/every-force-of-nature/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/every-force-of-nature/</guid><description>So, every force of nature showed
the shattered ways the crystal glowed.
A gemstone fit to lose our minds,
that let us know such things remote; the broken ways the aura binds</description></item><item><title>Fauna of the Second Realm</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/2nd-realm-fauna/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/2nd-realm-fauna/</guid><description>Minikin Minikin are a sapient rodent species native to the 2nd realm. They are descended from the European Red Squirrel, with a lifespan of 12-18 years, reaching maturity around 8 years of age.</description></item><item><title>Flora of the Second Realm</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/2nd-realm-flora/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/2nd-realm-flora/</guid><description>Nyuta Bushes Nyuta bushes are a type of bush native to the 2nd and 1st realms. They have red leaves and purple berries.</description></item><item><title>History of the Morellic Minikin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/history/morellic-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/history/morellic-history/</guid><description>Overview The Morellic race is a race of minikin descending from the Sarvaran, Aqhoran, and Corothic cultures. These cultures were forager nomads from the west, north, and east, who settled in the Sarvaran river basin due to it&amp;rsquo;s highly fertile soil and the Mora river&amp;rsquo;s seasonal flooding.</description></item><item><title>If Only (Draft 1, 22 Nov 2021)</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/drafts/draft-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/drafts/draft-1/</guid><description>Chapter 1 Woodlice, dirt, and leaves. These were the first things little Blueberry saw when he woke up. This environment he had found himself in seemed like a poor imitation of what he was used to, which was a constant supply of cucumber and the fibreglass tree stump he called home - but this wasn&amp;rsquo;t his home, this was something else.</description></item><item><title>If Only (Draft 2, 17 Oct 2023)</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/drafts/draft-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/drafts/draft-2/</guid><description>Chapter 1 People are made for one another, to live and love in the company of those they care about. But in the midst of the undergrowth, someone was left.</description></item><item><title>Minikin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/minikin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/minikin/</guid><description>Overview Minikin (spp. Anthrosciurus sapiens) are a small rodent species native to the 2nd Realm. They are arboreal omnivores which tend toward eating nuts and other plants, and descended from red squirrels from the 0th realm.</description></item><item><title>Phantasmarrhoea</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/illnesses/phantasmarrhoea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/illnesses/phantasmarrhoea/</guid><description>Overview Phantasmarrhoea (Sarvaran: Fantasmeyolh ) is a physiological condition that affects living beings. It causes those affected, known as Phantasms, to experience irreversable physical and mental effects, leading to the growth of Alucinarium on the body and psychosis.</description></item><item><title>Sarvara</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/sarvara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/sarvara/</guid><description>Overview Sarvara (Sarvaran: &amp;lsquo;Sarvárą&amp;rsquo; IPA: /sar.vá.rã/) was a Morellic city state and a civilisation whose society, territory, and culture extended beyond its original city walls.</description></item><item><title>Sarvaran Architecture</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/sarvara/sarvaran-architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/sarvara/sarvaran-architecture/</guid><description>Overview The architecture of Sarvara refers to the many styles and methods of building structures within the city state, and further settlements and outposts within its cultural sphere.</description></item><item><title>Sarvaran Instruments</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/sarvara/sarvaran-instruments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/sarvara/sarvaran-instruments/</guid><description>Overview Sarvaran culture was rich with artwork and innovation. The four most prominent fields in ancient Sarvara were pottery, poetry, architecture, and music.</description></item><item><title>Sarvaran Love Story</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/sarvaran-love-story/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/sarvaran-love-story/</guid><description>Premise The story is foremost about the romance between two Sarvaran minikin, the young Ibusa (also known as Bibu) and Madairh (also known as Mada).</description></item><item><title>Sharadism</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/illnesses/sharadism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/illnesses/sharadism/</guid><description>Overview Sharadism is a physiological condition that affects organic beings. It causes those affected, known as Sharadith1, to undergo many irreversable physical, mental, and spiritual changes, resulting in a grotesque appearance and insatiable need to consume the blood and flesh of others.</description></item><item><title>Soulstones</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/soulstone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/soulstone/</guid><description>Overview Soulstones are deposits of bitumen or asphalt where, in the presence of alucinara energy, the soul of a deceased organism may be stored after death.</description></item><item><title>The 2nd Realm</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/2nd-realm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/2nd-realm/</guid><description>Overview The 2nd realm is the 2nd ultra-essent realm, and is contra-essent to the -2nd realm. The 2nd realm&amp;rsquo;s main planet is Qherelh, inhabited by the native minikin.</description></item><item><title>The Angels</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/celestial-beings/the-angels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/celestial-beings/the-angels/</guid><description>Overview The angels are celestial beings created by the Judges to govern the elements of the cosmos. They are worshipped as parts of the pantheons of many Minikin cultures, and can be communicated with through dreams, visions, and prayer.</description></item><item><title>The Early Morellic Tribes</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/early-morellic-tribes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/early-morellic-tribes/</guid><description>Overview The early Morellic tribes were made up of nomadic, matrilineal clans living in the south of Tseireph during the minikin Mesolithic era, or Middle Stone Age.</description></item><item><title>The Judges</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/celestial-beings/the-judges/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/celestial-beings/the-judges/</guid><description>Overview The Judges are the two celestial beings from the beginning of the cosmos who created the universe, the spirits of darkness, and the angels.</description></item><item><title>The Language of Sarvara</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/sarvara/sarvaran-language/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/sarvara/sarvaran-language/</guid><description>Overview Sarvaran was a Morellic language spoken in the Sarvaran civilisation during the Minikin bronze-age. It was polysynthetic, head-final, and head-marking, with an SOV word order.</description></item><item><title>The Mind Controls</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/the-mind-controls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/the-mind-controls/</guid><description>A rodent sat atop the cliff of an inlet, its whole life built upon service to an instinct.
Staring down at the rocks upon which a wave rolls, here the world now makes sense, to the heart, so thoughts sink&amp;rsquo;d;</description></item><item><title>The Morellic Creation Story</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/morellic-creation-story/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/morellic-creation-story/</guid><description>Chapter One Before the days of our mothers, before the Lunuth was first planted, and before men and gods drew their first breaths, were all things ordered by the Judges.</description></item><item><title>The North Wind and the Sun</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/translations/the-north-wind-and-the-sun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/translations/the-north-wind-and-the-sun/</guid><description>Original Text The North Wind and the Sun were disputing which was the stronger, when a traveler came along wrapped in a warm cloak.</description></item><item><title>The Petrified Child</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/celestial-beings/the-petrified-child/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/celestial-beings/the-petrified-child/</guid><description>Overview The Petrified Child is a semi-corporeal deity which is worshipped by many minikin groups, including the Morellic minikin. The child&amp;rsquo;s duty is to destroy all evil according to its own moral code, protecting the cosmos1 from any living being who wishes to desecrate it.</description></item><item><title>The Sarvaran Epic Narrative</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/sarvaran-epic-narrative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/sarvaran-epic-narrative/</guid><description>SCRIPTURA EX MUNDO PRAE ET POST FRACTO Chapter 1 The Cosmos Given Shape Before Lunuth had first sprouted, before it had been ground into flour or baked into bread, the first Judge and the second Judge ruled the cosmos, to give it order.</description></item><item><title>The Spirits of Darkness</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/celestial-beings/the-spirits-of-darkness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/celestial-beings/the-spirits-of-darkness/</guid><description>Overview The spirits of darkness are celestial beings that were created by the second Judge behind the first&amp;rsquo;s back out of jealousy for the first&amp;rsquo;s superiority.</description></item><item><title>title</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/characters/grasscap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/characters/grasscap/</guid><description>%% What are the significant features which make this relevant to the plot? What patterns are there when it comes to description and properties?</description></item><item><title>Tseireph</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/tseireph/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/tseireph/</guid><description>Overview Tseireph is a continent of the planet Qherelh in the 2nd realm. It is notable for being the source of the Morellic Minikin, and the place where civilisation emerged1.</description></item><item><title>Watchstones</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/watchstones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/watchstones/</guid><description>Overview Watchstones are stones1 with eyes through which the Petrified Child sees, giving the deity a greater visual field and protecting those nearby from evil.</description></item></channel></rss>