<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>If Only You Set Me Free on</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in If Only You Set Me Free on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://book.pyxelm.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alucinara Energy</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/alucinara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/alucinara/</guid><description>Overview Alucinara, also known as magic, is a form of energy that alters the ways in which the natural world can operate.</description></item><item><title>Bushdeer</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/bushdeer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/bushdeer/</guid><description>Overview Bushdeer (Type Species spp. Floricervus Floricervus), native to the steppes of the 2nd and -1st realms, are a type of deer related to the Sika deer of Earth.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Gnats</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/cloud-gnats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/cloud-gnats/</guid><description>Overview Cloud Gnats are animal-like apparitions made of alucinariferous dust. They commonly appear as small animals, standing upright with their abdomen tapering off into a wispy tail.</description></item><item><title>Darkness</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/darkness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/darkness/</guid><description>Overview Darkness, similar to Alucinara, is a form of energy that forms the foundation of the Soul. It does this by enforcing the second laws of nature, which defined the methods by which spirits could operate.</description></item><item><title>Demi-Slugs</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/demi-slugs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/demi-slugs/</guid><description>%% What are the significant features which make this relevant to the plot? What patterns are there when it comes to description and properties?</description></item><item><title>Early History of the Minikin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/history/early-minikin-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/history/early-minikin-history/</guid><description>Timeline 5 MYA Minikin begin to diverge from the lineage that would become red squirrels Minikin ancestors are shifted from the 0th realm to the 2nd due to supernova 3 MYA The genus Anthrosciurus diverges from Sciurus Anthrosciurids begin to use tools 1 MYA Anthrosciurids begin to use fire and magic Language is developed in Anthrosciurids 300,000 YA Early Minikin evolve into Modern Minikin (Anthrosciurus arborensis) in northern Tséireph 200,00 YA First wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Eastern Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis occidentalis) migrate to the eastern continent and eastern islands Modern Minikin spread across whole of Tséireph 175,000 YA Second wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Southern Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis australis) migrate to southwestern continent 50,000 YA Third and final wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Insular Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis insulensis) diverge from Southern Minikin and continue to migrate south to the southwestern archipelago The various Minikin subspecies begin to spread and cohabitate with other races 10,000 YA Agriculture begins to be practised by Minikin, originating in fluvial areas with seasonal floods, especially the mediterranean-climate Sarvaran river basin.</description></item><item><title>Every Force of Nature</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/every-force-of-nature/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/every-force-of-nature/</guid><description>So, every force of nature showed
the shattered ways the crystal glowed.
A gemstone fit to lose our minds,
that let us know such things remote; the broken ways the aura binds</description></item><item><title>Fauna of the Second Realm</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/2nd-realm-fauna/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/2nd-realm-fauna/</guid><description>Minikin Minikin are a sapient rodent species native to the 2nd realm. They are descended from the European Red Squirrel, with a lifespan of 12-18 years, reaching maturity around 8 years of age.</description></item><item><title>Flora of the Second Realm</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/2nd-realm-flora/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/2nd-realm-flora/</guid><description>Nyuta Bushes Nyuta bushes are a type of bush native to the 2nd and 1st realms. They have red leaves and purple berries.</description></item><item><title>History of the Morellic Minikin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/history/morellic-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/history/morellic-history/</guid><description>Overview The Morellic race is a race of minikin descending from the Sarvaran, Aqhoran, and Corothic cultures. These cultures were forager nomads from the west, north, and east, who settled in the Sarvaran river basin due to it&amp;rsquo;s highly fertile soil and the Mora river&amp;rsquo;s seasonal flooding.</description></item><item><title>Minikin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/minikin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/fauna/minikin/</guid><description>Overview Minikin (spp. Anthrosciurus sapiens) are a small rodent species native to the 2nd Realm. They are arboreal omnivores which tend toward eating nuts and other plants, and descended from red squirrels from the 0th realm.</description></item><item><title>Morellic Clothing</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/clothing/morellic-clothing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/clothing/morellic-clothing/</guid><description>Overview Morellic clothing is characterised by three things: Shape, Colour, and Material. These three elements come together to create a morellic garment.</description></item><item><title>Phantasmarrhoea</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/phantasmarrhoea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/phantasmarrhoea/</guid><description>%% What are the significant features which make this relevant to the plot? What patterns are there when it comes to description and properties?</description></item><item><title>Soulstones</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/soulstone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/soulstone/</guid><description>Overview Soulstones are deposits of bitumen or asphalt where, in the presence of alucinara energy, the soul of a deceased organism may be stored after death.</description></item><item><title>The Mind Controls</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/the-mind-controls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/the-mind-controls/</guid><description>A rodent sat atop the cliff of an inlet, its whole life built upon service to an instinct.
Staring down at the rocks upon which a wave rolls, here the world now makes sense, to the heart, so thoughts sink&amp;rsquo;d;</description></item><item><title>The Petrified Child</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/deities/the-petrified-child/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/deities/the-petrified-child/</guid><description>Overview The Petrified Child is an entity with the purpose of governing evil. It accomplishes this through the use of watchstones and the turning of evildoers into baby meadows.</description></item><item><title>The Sarvaran Epic Narrative</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/sarvaran-epic-narrative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/writing/sarvaran-epic-narrative/</guid><description>SCRIPTURA EX MUNDO PRAE ET POST FRACTO Chapter 1 The Cosmos Given Shape Before Lunuth had first sprouted, before it had been ground into flour or baked into bread, the first Judge and the second Judge ruled the cosmos, to give it order.</description></item><item><title>The Story of Creation</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/creation-story/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/cosmology/creation-story/</guid><description>Overview The creation story of the universe is characterised by one main event - the shattering of the realms. The universe was created by the two Judges, and shattered by the spirits of darkness.</description></item><item><title>title</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/characters/grasscap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/characters/grasscap/</guid><description>%% What are the significant features which make this relevant to the plot? What patterns are there when it comes to description and properties?</description></item><item><title>Watchstones</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/watchstones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/watchstones/</guid><description>Overview Watchstones are a type of entity through which the The Petrified Child can see, giving it a greater visual range.</description></item></channel></rss>