<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lores on</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/</link><description>Recent content in Lores on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aqhoran Culture</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/groups/aqhoran/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/groups/aqhoran/</guid><description>Overview The Aqhoran culture was a Minikin culture native to the Sarvaran river basin, on the southern coast of Tséireph.</description></item><item><title>Early History of the Minikin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/history/early-minikin-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/history/early-minikin-history/</guid><description>Timeline 5 MYA Minikin begin to diverge from the lineage that would become red squirrels Minikin ancestors are shifted from the 0th realm to the 2nd due to supernova 3 MYA The genus Anthrosciurus diverges from Sciurus Anthrosciurids begin to use tools 1 MYA Anthrosciurids begin to use fire and magic Language is developed in Anthrosciurids 300,000 YA Early Minikin evolve into Modern Minikin (Anthrosciurus arborensis) in northern Tséireph 200,00 YA First wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Eastern Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis occidentalis) migrate to the eastern continent and eastern islands Modern Minikin spread across whole of Tséireph 175,000 YA Second wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Southern Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis australis) migrate to southwestern continent 50,000 YA Third and final wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Insular Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis insulensis) diverge from Southern Minikin and continue to migrate south to the southwestern archipelago The various Minikin subspecies begin to spread and cohabitate with other races 10,000 YA Agriculture begins to be practised by Minikin, originating in fluvial areas with seasonal floods in Mediterranean climates.</description></item><item><title>Lhantana Culture</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/groups/lhantana/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/groups/lhantana/</guid><description>Overview The Aqhoran culture was a Minikin culture native to the Sarvaran river basin, on the southern coast of Tséireph.</description></item><item><title>Sarvaran History</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/history/sarvaran-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/history/sarvaran-history/</guid><description>Overview Sarvara was a river and later became the name of an imperial Morellic civilisation. The name is taken from the Sarvaran language, meaning &amp;lsquo;our river.</description></item><item><title>The Creation Story</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/creation-story/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/creation-story/</guid><description>Overview In this note, I will describe the canonical creation story. In-world, it is believed by the Morellic Minikin, but was diverged from or was abandoned by many other groups who believe other stories.</description></item><item><title>The Sarvaran River Basin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/locations/sarvaran-basin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/locations/sarvaran-basin/</guid><description>Overview The Sarvaran river basin is a river basin on the southern coast of Tséireph. It&amp;rsquo;s main river is the river Sarvara, which flows from Lake Jerrun in the Sarvaran highlands.</description></item><item><title>Tseiréph</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/locations/tseireph/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/locations/tseireph/</guid><description>Overview Tseiréph is the central continent of the 2nd Realm.</description></item></channel></rss>