<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>featured on</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/tags/featured/</link><description>Recent content in featured on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://book.pyxelm.xyz/tags/featured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alucinara</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/deities/alucinara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/deities/alucinara/</guid><description>Overview Alucinara, also known as &amp;lsquo;Magic,&amp;rsquo; is a deity that allows the first laws of nature to act in place of the second.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Gnats</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/cloud-gnats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/cloud-gnats/</guid><description>Overview Cloud Gnats are animal-like apparitions made of alucinariferous dust. They commonly appear as small animals, standing upright with their abdomen tapering off into a wispy tail.</description></item><item><title>Early History of the Minikin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/history/early-minikin-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/history/early-minikin-history/</guid><description>Timeline 5 MYA Minikin begin to diverge from the lineage that would become red squirrels Minikin ancestors are shifted from the 0th realm to the 2nd due to supernova 3 MYA The genus Anthrosciurus diverges from Sciurus Anthrosciurids begin to use tools 1 MYA Anthrosciurids begin to use fire and magic Language is developed in Anthrosciurids 300,000 YA Early Minikin evolve into Modern Minikin (Anthrosciurus arborensis) in northern Tséireph 200,00 YA First wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Eastern Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis occidentalis) migrate to the eastern continent and eastern islands Modern Minikin spread across whole of Tséireph 175,000 YA Second wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Southern Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis australis) migrate to southwestern continent 50,000 YA Third and final wave of minikin migration takes place Ancestors of Insular Minikin (subspecies Anthrosciurus arborensis insulensis) diverge from Southern Minikin and continue to migrate south to the southwestern archipelago The various Minikin subspecies begin to spread and cohabitate with other races 10,000 YA Agriculture begins to be practised by Minikin, originating in fluvial areas with seasonal floods in Mediterranean climates.</description></item><item><title>Enchantment</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/enchantment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/enchantment/</guid><description>Overview Enchantment is the term given to the presence of the First Laws in a being or item&amp;rsquo;s behaviour. This means that if a being or object is enchanted, it will act strangely, in predictable or unpredictable ways depending on the specific enchantment.</description></item><item><title>Fortuitary Gland</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/fortuitary-gland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/fortuitary-gland/</guid><description>Overview Fortuitary glands are glands dedicated to the secretion of Alucinarium, and are integral to the use of Alucinara in biological processes or tools.</description></item><item><title>History of the Morellic Minikin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/histories/morellic-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/histories/morellic-history/</guid><description>Morellic Minikin The Morellic race of minikin originated in Tséireph, and had their genesis in the Mora Tribe.
The Mora Tribe The Mora were a nomadic pastoralist tribe with fair skin and hairy extremeties.</description></item><item><title>Minikin</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/species/fauna/minikin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/species/fauna/minikin/</guid><description>Overview Minikin (spp. Anthrosciurus sapiens) are a small rodent species native to the 2nd Realm. They are arboreal omnivores which tend toward eating nuts and other plants, and descended from red squirrels from the 0th realm.</description></item><item><title>Sky Islands</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/sky-islands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/sky-islands/</guid><description>Overview Generally, sky islands are large animal-shaped islands which float above the surface of the ground. They often feature self-sustaining ecosystems atop them, with a forest or grassland on the topside, and a rocky underside which changes shape due to Alucinara influence.</description></item><item><title>Soulstones</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/soulstone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/soulstone/</guid><description>Overview Soulstones are deposits of bitumen or asphalt where, in the presence of alucinara energy, the soul of a deceased organism may be stored after death.</description></item><item><title>Symbols</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/symbols/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/symbols/</guid><description>Overview Symbols are shapes or images through which alucinara energy can be channeled for a specific effect. This is achieved as symbols emulate the beauty of the world pre-shattering.</description></item><item><title>The Creation Story</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/creation-story/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/lore/creation-story/</guid><description>Overview In this note, I will describe the canonical creation story. In-world, it is believed by the Morellic Minikin, but was diverged from or was abandoned by many other groups who believe other stories.</description></item><item><title>The Darkness</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/deities/the-darkness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/deities/the-darkness/</guid><description>Overview The Darkness, also known as &amp;lsquo;Life,&amp;rsquo; is a deity that governs the way in which living beings operate. Derived from the force of Life, it lacks a physical form, functioning as life energy.</description></item><item><title>The Golden Ape</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/deities/the-golden-ape/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/deities/the-golden-ape/</guid><description>Overview The golden ape, also known as &amp;lsquo;Truth,&amp;rsquo; is a deity through which all knowledge is learnt, practised, and made known.</description></item><item><title>The Petrified Child</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/deities/the-petrified-child/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/deities/the-petrified-child/</guid><description>Overview The Petrified Child, also known as &amp;lsquo;Goodness,&amp;rsquo; is a deity that regulates and destroys those who commit evil acts. It descends from the pre-shattering force of Goodness, travels by floating metres above the ground, and can shift across realms at its own discretion.</description></item><item><title>Watchstones</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/watchstones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/phenomena/watchstones/</guid><description>Overview Watchstones are artificial patrols invented by the Sarvaran minikin for the purpose of giving The Petrified Child a greater visual range.</description></item></channel></rss>