<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>flora on</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/tags/flora/</link><description>Recent content in flora on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://book.pyxelm.xyz/tags/flora/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asaran</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/asaran/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/asaran/</guid><description>Overview Asaran trees are a species of evergreen conifer trees native to the mediterranean regions of the 2nd realm. They bear small, berry-like cones, which are used in cooking, and light wood which is used to make tools.</description></item><item><title>Canara</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/canara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/canara/</guid><description>Overview Canara is a type of nut, the fruit of the Canara tree. Canara trees are native to the continental forests and mediterranean regions of the 2nd realm, being a mainstay of Morellic cooking.</description></item><item><title>Creepvine</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/creepvine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/creepvine/</guid><description>Overview Creepvine is a species of plant native to the forests of the -1st and -3rd realms. It commonly grows upon other plants, such as ribwood, acting as a parasitic weed.</description></item><item><title>Dhajar</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/dhajar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/dhajar/</guid><description>Overview Dhajar trees are a species of coniferous tree native to the continental forests of the 2nd realm. Their wood is a common material in carpentry, especially in Coroth and the Empire of the Petrified Child.</description></item><item><title>Elkwort</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/elkwort/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/elkwort/</guid><description>Overview Elkwort is a herb native to the continental regions of the 2nd and -1st realms, related to ferns. It is a common garden plant, used in Corothic and Stonechild Imperial cooking.</description></item><item><title>Glara</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/glara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/glara/</guid><description>Overview Glara are a species of tree native to the tropical rainforests of the 2nd and -2nd realms. They bear luminescent fruit, common in Nethic food.</description></item><item><title>Lunaflower</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/lunaflower/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/lunaflower/</guid><description>Overview Lunaflower is a plant native to the 2nd and -3rd realms.</description></item><item><title>Lunuth</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/lunuth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/lunuth/</guid><description>Overview Lunuth wheat is a type of domesticated cereal grain native to the 2nd realm. It is a staple crop for many cultures, especially of Sarvara, by whom it was domesticated.</description></item><item><title>Nyuta</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/nyuta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/nyuta/</guid><description>Overview Nyuta is a type of berry, the fruit of the Nyuta bush. Nyuta bushes are native to the plains of the 2nd and 1st realms, and their leaves form the main ingredient in Nyuta tea; they are scarcely found aside from orchards, and are a high-class symbol.</description></item><item><title>Pelen</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/pelen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/pelen/</guid><description>Overview Pelen is a type of root vegetable, similar to carrots, native to the plains regions of the 2nd and 3rd realms.</description></item><item><title>Ribwood</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/ribwood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/ribwood/</guid><description>Overview Ribwood trees are a species of tree native to the forests and jungles of the -3rd realm.
Appearance Ribwood trees are long and winding, with eponymous ribbed bark that repeats in rings along the trunk.</description></item><item><title>Sarkitwara</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/sarkitwara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/sarkitwara/</guid><description>Overview Sarkitwara is a type of citron fruit, the fruit of the Sarkitwara tree. Sarkitwara trees are native to the mediterranean and hot wilderness regions of the 2nd and 1st realms, and are a common food item for their cohabitant fauna.</description></item><item><title>Sweetrice</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/sweetrice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/sweetrice/</guid><description>Overview Sweetrice is a type of domesticated cereal grain native to the southwestern continent of the 2nd realm. It is a staple crop for the minikin of Aqhor, who brought it to the Sarvaran river basin from their homeland.</description></item></channel></rss>