<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>woody-plants on</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/tags/woody-plants/</link><description>Recent content in woody-plants on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://book.pyxelm.xyz/tags/woody-plants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asaran</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/asaran/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/asaran/</guid><description>Overview Asaran trees are a species of evergreen conifer trees native to the mediterranean regions of the 2nd realm. They bear small, berry-like cones, which are used in cooking, and light wood which is used to make tools.</description></item><item><title>Canara</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/canara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/canara/</guid><description>Overview Canara is a type of nut, the fruit of the Canara tree. Canara trees are native to the continental forests and mediterranean regions of the 2nd realm, being a mainstay of Morellic cooking.</description></item><item><title>Dhajar</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/dhajar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/dhajar/</guid><description>Overview Dhajar trees are a species of coniferous tree native to the continental forests of the 2nd realm. Their wood is a common material in carpentry, especially in Coroth and the Empire of the Petrified Child.</description></item><item><title>Nyuta</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/nyuta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/nyuta/</guid><description>Overview Nyuta is a type of berry, the fruit of the Nyuta bush. Nyuta bushes are native to the plains of the 2nd and 1st realms, and their leaves form the main ingredient in Nyuta tea; they are scarcely found aside from orchards, and are a high-class symbol.</description></item><item><title>Ribwood</title><link>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/ribwood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://book.pyxelm.xyz/flora/ribwood/</guid><description>Overview Ribwood trees are a species of tree native to the forests and jungles of the -3rd realm.
Appearance Ribwood trees are long and winding, with eponymous ribbed bark that repeats in rings along the trunk.</description></item></channel></rss>